<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data name="Higher Resolution UI Enhancer" author="Nexus_314" description="This mod combines the effects of Higher Resolution Navigation,  Higher Resolution Radar, UI Enhancer, Captain Controls, Albatross AWACS and other further improvements.

Current Version: 2.2

https://github.com/NexusQuile/CC2-Higher-Resolution

[h2]Source Mods[/h2]

[b]UI Enhancer (by QunatX)[/b]
https://github.com/Quantx/CC2-UI-Enhancer
Steam Workshop: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2761300794.
Version 2024/03/18 (GitHub)

[b]Captain Controls (by Mr Scoot)[/b]
Steam Workshop: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2824746567.
Version 2024/03/17 (Steam)

[b]Albatross AWACS (by Thumblegudget)[/b]
Steam Workshop: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2891723169
Version v2 2024/03/11 (Steam)

[h2]Higher Resolution Changes:[/h2]

This Mod makes the following further changes:

[b]Navigation Screens[/b]
[list]
[*]Increases resolution of the three lower helm screens
[*]Changes the start up display of the main helm screens
[*]The Centre Screen now defaults to display ocean current and sets zoom level to match the left screen to give a better overview of the map
[*]Right Screen now defaults to display ocean depth and sets zoom level to match the left screen to give a better overview of the map
[/list]

[b]Radar Screen[/b]
[list]
[*]Increases the resolution of the ship's radar screen
[*]Adds ID number of detected aircraft and ships (green)
[*]Adds direction heading (white line) to aircarft and ships (white)
[*]Change ship heading line to white and sweep line to green
[*]Adds 15deg tick marks around the perimeter of the radar circle 
[/list]

[b]CCTV[/b]
[list]
[*]increases the resolution of the ship's CCTV screen
[*]CCTV camera will now show the view of aircraft being held on deck (rather than default back to showing the hanger)
[*]CCTV camera will now show a banner when the aircraft being shown is being held on deck
[*]CCTV camera will now stay with a launching vehicle and not cycle between land and air views in auto mode.
[/list]

[b]Control Screens[/b]
[list]
[*]added option to show vehicle ID on waypoints of firendly vehicles. Waypoint does not shown ID when it is a dock command on a carrier.
[*] added option to show looping icon can all the waypoint links that are in the loop - not just the last. This can be set per control screen. 
[*] added option to show loadout of vehicles (land, air, Needlefish and Swordfish) in top right when hovering over the unit or also when hovering over any waypoint).
[/list]

">
</data>